pickup Tupperware
pickup pie
place pie in Tupperware
place in Tupperware
pickup pie
place pie
put pie
pickup pie
move pie
pick up lid
close Tupperware
pickup paper towel
get paper towel
pickup Tupperware
dry Tupperware
hold Tupperware and dry Tupperware
pickup pie
put in Tupperware
pick up pie
put up pie
pickup pie
put pie
Place tupperware
pickup lid
dry lid
hold and dry lid
close tupperware
pickup two tupperwares
place tupperwares
open fridge
move remove salad from fridge
put salad plate
move stuff in fridge
move eggs in fridge
put tupperware in fridge
put Tupperware in fridge
move tupperware
close fridge
[END SUBTITLE]